# Ayodeji Adebola

Ikorodu, Lagos, Nigeria



ayodejiadebola20@gmail.com



08096362793



linkedin.com/in/ayodeji-adebola-profile

# Summary

I have 3+ years of experience building web applications using mostly javascript libraries and frameworks, other times I use ASP.NET. I find building of software interesting, intriguing and relatively easy. I am currently learning react expo for mobile applications. So far, it's been good to work on the projects i have had. Looking for exciting challenges and opportunities that come my way. If you feel like we can make something better, feel free to reach out to me.

## **Experience**



**Favourite Doctor** 

Jan 2022 - Present (5 months +)



### Software developer intern

Sophia ERP Limited

Apr 2021 - Oct 2021 (7 months)

1. I developed web applications using ASP.NET(VB.NET) and

Microsoft SQL

- 2. I researched and developed teaching materials and user guides for some of the software applications made by Sophia ERP Limited.
- 3. I taught students how to create websites with HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.
- 4. I taught students about cloud computing and deploying web applications on Microsoft Azure.

# **Summer Trainee**

Platinum IT Solutions

Nov 2016 - Jun 2018 (1 year 8 months)

- 1. Installation of CCTV
- 2. Computer troubleshooting and repair
- 3. Installation of Wireless connection

### **Education**



### Federal University of Technology Akure

Bachelor's of engineering (in view), Computer Engineering 2016 - 2022

### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Certification of volunteering YIEE Youth Initiative for Economic Empowerment
- Note: The content of the content of
- in Graphic design SHAW ACADEMY UK LIMITED

# **Skills**

Web Development • Graphic Design • Computer Repair • Computer Networking • JavaScript • Node.js • MongoDB • React.js • ASP.NET • PostgreSQL